Finding Aid for the J. Warren Perry Collection of Photographs, circa 1910-1971
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Productions, circa 1910-1971, II.; 402 photographs
  - Macbeth, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 22, Item C22-060)
  - Macbeth, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 22, Item C22-061)
  - Nabucco, Act I, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 22, Item C22-062)
  - Nabucco, Act III, scene 2, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 22, Item C22-063)
  - Nabucco, Act IV, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; Marchiori (Box 22, Item C22-064)
  - Nabucco, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 22, Item C22-065)
  - Nabucco, Act I, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Francesco Leoni (Genoa, Italy) (Box 22, Item C22-066)
  - Nabucco, Act II, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Irifoto (Box 22, Item C22-067)
  - Otello, Act III, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 22, Item C22-068)
  - Otello, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 22, Item C22-069)
  - Otello, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 22, Item C22-070)
  - Otello, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 22, Item C22-071)
  - Otello, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Barratt's Photo Press (London, England) (Box 22, Item C22-072)
  - Otello, Act I, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 22, Item C22-073)
  - Otello, Act III, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 22, Item C22-074)
  - Otello, 1958-1959?, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 22, Item C22-075)
  - Otello, Act II, 1955?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 22, Item C22-076)
  - Otello, Act II, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Parolin (Verona, Italy) (Box 22, Item C22-077)
  - Otello, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Irifoto (Box 22, Item C22-078)
  - Otello, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 22, Item C22-079)
  - Rigoletto, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-001)
  - Rigoletto, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-002)
  - Rigoletto, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-003)
  - Rigoletto, Act III, 1949-1950, 1 black and white photograph; Maggio Musicale Fiorentino (Box 23, Item C23-004)
  - Rigoletto, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-005)
  - Rigoletto, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-006)
  - Rigoletto, 1951-1955?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 23, Item C23-007)
  - Rigoletto, 1953?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 23, Item C23-008)
  - Rigoletto, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Irifoto (Box 23, Item C23-009)
  - Simon Boccanegra, Act I, scene 2, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 23, Item C23-010)
  - Simon Boccanegra, Act I, scene 2, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 23, Item C23-011)
  - Simon Boccanegra, Act I, scene 1, 1955?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 23, Item C23-012)
  - Simon Boccanegra, Act I, scene 2, 1955?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 23, Item C23-013)
  - Simon Boccanegra, Act II, 1955?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 23, Item C23-014)
  - Simon Boccanegra, Act III, 1955?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 23, Item C23-015)
  - Simon Boccanegra, with Leonard Warren, Richard Tucker, and Mary Curtis-Verna, 1960 March 1, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 23, Item C23-016)
  - La Traviata, Act II, scene 2, with Giuseppe DiStefano (?), 1955-1956?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 23, Item C23-017)
  - La Traviata, Act III, 1955-1956?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 23, Item C23-018)
  - La Traviata, Act I, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 23, Item C23-019)
  - La Traviata, Act I, 1959?, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 23, Item C23-020)
  - La Traviata, Act III, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 23, Item C23-021)
  - La Traviata, Act III, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 23, Item C23-022)
  - La Traviata, Act IV, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 23, Item C23-023)
  - La Traviata, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 23, Item C23-024)
  - La Traviata, Act I, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-025)
  - La Traviata, Act II, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Reale (Rome, Italy) (Box 23, Item C23-026)
  - Il Trovatore, Act I, scene 2, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-027)
  - Il Trovatore, Act II, scene 2, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-028)
  - Il Trovatore, Act III, scene 1, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-029)
  - Il Trovatore, Act III, scene 2, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-030)
  - Il Trovatore, convent scene, 1950-1951?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 23, Item C23-031)
  - Il Trovatore, 1971?, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 23, Item C23-032)
  - Les v?pres siciliennes, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Maggio Musicale Fiorentino (Box 23, Item C23-033)
  - Der fliegende Holländer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Ottica (Bologna, Italy) (Box 23, Item C23-034)
  - Der fliegende Holländer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-035)
  - Der fliegende Holländer, 1960 March, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 23, Item C23-036)
  - Lohengrin, Act I, 1959, 1 black and white photograph; Buhs, Ilse (Box 23, Item C23-037)
  - Lohengrin, Act I, 1959, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-038)
  - Lohengrin, Act II, 1959, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-039)
  - Lohengrin, Act II, 1959, 1 black and white photograph; Buhs, Ilse (Box 23, Item C23-040)
  - Lohengrin, Act III, 1959, 1 black and white photograph; Buhs, Ilse (Box 23, Item C23-041)
  - Lohengrin, Act I, 1957-1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 23, Item C23-042)
  - Lohengrin, Act II, 1957-1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 23, Item C23-043)
  - Lohengrin, Act III, 1957-1958?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 23, Item C23-044)
  - Lohengrin, Act II, 1952, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 23, Item C23-045)
  - Die Mesitersinger von Nürnberg, 1959, 1 black and white photograph; Buhs, Ilse (Box 23, Item C23-046)
  - Die Mesitersinger von Nürnberg, Act II, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-047)
  - Die Mesitersinger von Nürnberg, Act II, 1959?, 1 black and white photograph; Falk, Adolf (Box 23, Item C23-048)
  - Die Mesitersinger von Nürnberg, Act III, 1959?, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-049)
  - Die Mesitersinger von Nürnberg, Act III, 1959, 1 black and white photograph; Buhs, Ilse (Box 23, Item C23-050)
  - Die Mesitersinger von Nürnberg, Act III, 1959, 1 black and white photograph; Buhs, Ilse (Box 23, Item C23-051)
  - Die Mesitersinger von Nürnberg, Feb. 17, 1953?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 23, Item C23-052)
  - Die Mesitersinger von Nürnberg, 1954 Nov. 11, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 23, Item C23-053)
  - Die Mesitersinger von Nürnberg, 1954 Nov. 11, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 23, Item C23-054)
  - Parsifal, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-055)
  - Parsifal, Act I, 1954-1956, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-056)
  - Parsifal, Act I, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-057)
  - Parsifal, Act II, 1956-1962, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-058)
  - Parsifal, Act III, 1956-1962, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-059)
  - Der Ring des Nibelungen. Das Rheingold, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-060)
  - Der Ring des Nibelungen. Das Rheingold, final act, 1951?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 23, Item C23-061)
  - Der Ring des Nibelungen. Das Rheingold, final act, 1948?, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-062)
  - Der Ring des Nibelungen. Die Walküre, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Eysell, Heinz (Box 23, Item C23-063)
  - Der Ring des Nibelungen. Die Walküre, Act III, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-064)
  - Der Ring des Nibelungen. Die Walküre, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 23, Item C23-065)
  - Der Ring des Nibelungen. Die Walküre, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 23, Item C23-066)
  - Der Ring des Nibelungen. Die Walküre, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-067)
  - Der Ring des Nibelungen. Siegfried, Act I, forging of the sword, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-068)
  - Der Ring des Nibelungen. Siegfried, Act III, 1954-1957, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-069)
  - Der Ring des Nibelungen. Siegfried, Act III, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Festspiele Bayreuth (Box 23, Item C23-070)
  - Der Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung, Act II, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-071)
  - Der Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung, Act II, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Falk, Adolf (Box 23, Item C23-072)
  - Tannhäuser, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-073)
  - Tannhäuser, Act II, 1954?, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-074)
  - Tannhäuser, Act II, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-075)
  - Tannhäuser, Act III, 1954?, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-076)
  - Tannhäuser, Act I, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 23, Item C23-077)
  - Tristan und Isolde, Act I, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-078)
  - Tristan und Isolde, Act I, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 23, Item C23-079)
  - Tristan und Isolde, Act I, 1959, 1 black and white photograph; Buhs, Ilse (Box 23, Item C23-080)
  - Tristan und Isolde cast, 1958 Nov. 1, 7, 10, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 23, Item C23-081)
  - Tristan und Isolde, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 23, Item C23-082)
  - Tristan und Isolde, 1955?, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 23, Item C23-083)
  - Tristan und Isolde, Act II, 1959?, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 23, Item C23-084)
  - Troilus and Cressida, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Levi (Florence, Italy) (Box 23, Item C23-085)
  - Troilus and Cressida, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-086)
  - Troilus and Cressida, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-087)
  - Troilus and Cressida, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-088)
  - Troilus and Cressida, Act I, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 23, Item C23-089)
  - Troilus and Cressida, Act I, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-090)
  - Francesca da Rimini, Act II, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 23, Item C23-091)
  - Francesca da Rimini, Act II, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 23, Item C23-092)
  - Giulietta e Romeo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 23, Item C23-093)
- Ensembles, circa 1910-1971, III.; 47 photographs
  Photographs of ensembles, ranging from string quartets to symphony orchestras.
  Arranged alphabetically by ensemble name.
  - Moscow Radio Symphony Orchestra conducted by Nikolai Anosov on 200th anniversary of Bach's death, 1950, 1 black and white photograph; Ozersky, M (Box 24, Item C24-001)
  - Berlin Philharmonic with Herbert von Karajan, conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-002)
  - Berlin Philharmonic with Herbert von Karajan, conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-003)
  - Boston Pops Tour Orchestra with Arthur Fiedler, conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-004)
  - Boston Pops Orchestra with Arthur Fiedler, conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-005)
  - Boston Symphony Orchestra with Charles Munch, conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fay Foto Service (Boston, Mass.) (Box 24, Item C24-006)
  - Budapest String Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-007)
  - Carabinieri Band of Rome, Domenico Fantini conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Angel Records (Box 24, Item C24-008)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, Fritz Reiner conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-009)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, Fritz Reiner conductor, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-010)
  - Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra, Thor Johnson, conductor, 1955-1956, 1 black and white photograph; KLT Photos (Cincinnati, Ohio) (Box 24, Item C24-011)
  - Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra, Thor Johnson, conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; KLT Photos (Cincinnati, Ohio) (Box 24, Item C24-012)
  - Cleveland Orchestra, George Szell conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-013)
  - Concertgebouworkest Amsterdam, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-014)
  - Concertgebouworkest Amsterdam, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Photex - J. W. Verhoef (Amsterdam, Netherlands) (Box 24, Item C24-015)
  - Dallas Symphony, Walter Hendl conductor, 1949-1959, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-016)
  - Detroit Symphony, Paul Paray conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-017)
  - Figueroa Quintet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fotografia Arteaga (Box 24, Item C24-018)
  - Hallé Orchestra, Sir John Barbirolli conductor?, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-019)
  - Hallé Orchestra, Sir John Barbirolli conductor?, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-020)
  - Houston Symphony Orchestra, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-021)
  - Houston Symphony Orchestra, Leopold Stokowski conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-022)
  - Indianapolis Symphony Orchestra, Fabien Sevitsky conductor?, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-023)
  - Juilliard String Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Darby, Eileen (Box 24, Item C24-024)
  - Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra, Alfred Wallenstein conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Rothschild Photo (Box 24, Item C24-025)
  - Louisville Orchestra, Robert Whitney conductor, 1955-1956, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-026)
  - Minneapolis Symphony, Antal Dorati conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-027)
  - I Musici, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-028)
  - I Musici, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-029)
  - NBC Symphony, Arturo Toscanini conducting in Carnegie Hall, 1953-1954?, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-030)
  - Sir Malcolm Sargent conducting at Usher Hall, Edinburgh Festival, 1951?, 1 black and white photograph; British Travel and Holidays Association (Box 24, Item C24-031)
  - New York Philharmonic, Bruno Walter conductor, Edinburgh Festival Chorus, 1951, 1 black and white photograph; British Travel and Holidays Association (Box 24, Item C24-032)
  - New York Philharmonic at Carnegie Hall, 1955-1956, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-033)
  - Paganini Quartet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Homer (Hollywood, Calif.) (Box 24, Item C24-034)
  - Philharmonia Orchestra, Herbert von Karajan conductor, Royal Festival Hall, London, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-035)
  - Philadelphia Orchestra, Eugene Ormandy conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-036)
  - Robert Shaw Chorale, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-037)
  - Robert Shaw Chorale, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-038)
  - Rochester Philharmonic, Erich Leinsdorf conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Loulen Studio (Rochester, N.Y.) (Box 24, Item C24-039)
  - Royal Philharmonic Orchestra, Paul Kletzki conductor, Royal Festival Hall, London, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-040)
  - Royal Philharmonic Orchestra, Royal Festival Hall, London, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Colliers, Ltd (Box 24, Item C24-041)
  - San Francisco Symphony, Enrique Jorda conductor, 1955?, 1 black and white photograph; Strohmeyer (Box 24, Item C24-042)
  - Pierre Monteux receives standing ovation as conductor, San Francisco Symphony, 1952, 1 black and white photograph; Strohmeyer (Box 24, Item C24-043)
  - Symphony of the Air, Leonard Bernstein conductor, Carnegie Hall, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mazelis, V. (New York, N.Y.) (Box 24, Item C24-044)
  - Reader's Digest article about Symphony of the Air, 1955 August, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-045)
  - Reader's Digest article about Symphony of the Air, 1955 August, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-046)
  - Reader's Digest article about Symphony of the Air, 1955 August, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-047)
  - Vienna Philharmonic, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-048)
  - Vienna Symphony Orchestra at Athens Festival, 1957 Aug. 23, 1 black and white photograph; Harissiadis, D. A (Box 24, Item C24-049)
  - Virtuosi di Roma, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 24, Item C24-050)
- Concert Halls, circa 1910-1971, IV.; 193 photographs
  Concert halls and other performing venues such as outdoor amphitheaters.
  Arranged alphabetically by city and then by hall (with exception of Tanglewood, filed under T).
  - Front of Concertgebouw, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-001)
  - Gina Bachauer with Athens Festival Orchestra at Odeon of Herodes Atticus, with Parthenon in background, 1956 Aug., 1 black and white photograph; Harissiadis, D. A (Box 25, Item C25-002)
  - Odeon of Herodes Atticus, with Parthenon in background, 1957 Aug., 1 black and white photograph; Harissiadis, D. A (Box 25, Item C25-003)
  - Crowd exiting Odeon of Herodes Atticus, 1957 Sept., 1 black and white photograph; Harissiadis, D. A (Box 25, Item C25-004)
  - Drawing of Festspielhaus Bayreuth stage, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-005)
  - Festspielhaus Bayreuth, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lauterwasser (Festspiele Bayreuth) (Box 25, Item C25-006)
  - Indiana University Auditorium, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-007)
  - Indiana University Auditorium, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-008)
  - Stage of Indiana University Auditorium, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-009)
  - Interior of Indiana University Auditorium, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-010)
  - Teatro Comunale (Bologna), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Villani, A. & Figli (Box 25, Item C25-011)
  - Teatro Comunale (Bologna), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-012)
  - Teatro Comunale (Bologna), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Zagnoli (Bologna, Italy) (Box 25, Item C25-013)
  - Boston Symphony Hall, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Brook, John, Boston (Box 25, Item C25-014)
  - Teatro Colon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-015)
  - Teatro Colon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-016)
  - Teatro Colon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-017)
  - Teatro Colon, 1956 May 25, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-018)
  - Teatro Colon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-019)
  - Teatro Colon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-020)
  - Teatro Colon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-021)
  - Central City Opera House, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-022)
  - Central City Opera House, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-023)
  - Civic Opera House (Chicago), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Chicago Architectural Photographing Company (Box 25, Item C25-024)
  - Civic Opera House (Chicago), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Chicago Architectural Photographing Company (Box 25, Item C25-025)
  - Chicago Orchestra Hall, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-026)
  - Elena Nikolaidi and Nicolai Malko, conductor at Grant Park Band Shell final concert, 1949 Aug. 21, 1 black and white photograph; Chicago Park District (Box 25, Item C25-027)
  - Grant Park Band Shell with Chicago skyline, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Chicago Park District (Box 25, Item C25-028)
  - Civic Opera House (Chicago), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Chicago Architectural Photographing Company (Box 25, Item C25-029)
  - Civic Opera House (Chicago), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Chicago Architectural Photographing Company (Box 25, Item C25-030)
  - Cincinnati Summer Opera Pavillion, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-031)
  - Cincinnati Summer Opera Pavillion, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-032)
  - Aerial view of Cleveland with Cleveland Public Auditorium, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Miller-Ertler Studios (Cleveland, Ohio) (Box 25, Item C25-033)
  - Cleveland Public Auditorium, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Miller-Ertler Studios (Cleveland, Ohio) (Box 25, Item C25-034)
  - Cleveland Public Auditorium, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Miller-Ertler Studios (Cleveland, Ohio) (Box 25, Item C25-035)
  - Severance Hall (Cleveland), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Moss Photo (New York, N.Y.) (Box 25, Item C25-036)
  - Cleveland Music Hall, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-037)
  - Cleveland Music Hall, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 25, Item C25-038)